Our worst fears were finally realized.
Stop babbling!
Come on!
Your clothes are going to fall off!
So we'll need diapers and...
...milk?
Boobs?
A young girl
can't produce breast milk!
Diapers, bottle, powdered milk...
And we'll need hot water.
There, there.
I never thought I'd get
to carry Iori like this.
Nothing's happened to Taichi,
and Heartseed hasn't shown up.
A lot of things are different
this time around.
Y-Yeah...
Sis!
Anzu!
And Mihashi-san.
Why are you here?
Who are they?
Kiriyama's sister and a friend
from when she practiced karate.
You were acting strange,
so after I talked to Mihashi-san,
we decided to follow you.
Why is there a baby?
Um...
You keep them busy.
Let's go!
Wait!
Hold on!
You're not getting away.
Start by explaining the baby.
What do you mean?
Don't tell me that you
had a baby with him?
Of course not!
No, you're wrong.
Then the person holding
the baby was the mother?
No!
What?!
But assuming that you're the father...
Don't assume that.
Then how do you explain the
love triangle we have here?
There isn't a triangle!
I sent my sister home.
It'll be a pain to explain later.
Hey, Kiriyama...
What club are you in right now?
Huh? The Student Cultural Society.
What do you do?
Um...
We gather in the clubroom
to talk and have fun.
What does that accomplish?
Why do you ask that?
Are you doing anything at all?
Is there any purpose to your life?
Wh-Why do I need to have a purpose?
Look at how weak you've become.
Enough is enough!
Why?
Why are you attacking me?!
What happened to the cool you?!
Why does it matter how I used to be?!
I'm saying that right now
you pale in comparison
to your former self!
Were you lying to me back then?
What about the promise you made?!
I already said
I don't remember any promise!
I'm going to make you wake up.
Fight me!
Mihashi-san, have you
ever defeated me before?
W-Wait, are you serious?
Kiriyama!
And what happened?
Kiriyama was soundly beaten.
Anyway, she left after we
promised to explain later.
Hey, Iori!
Don't get too far away!
Cheer up, Nana's sister!
I know!
We can play games with Nana!
She said that she bought a
really fun game the other day!
Shut up! I'm Kiriyama Yui!
Oh, er...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Oh, no...
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
Man, why do I keep mistaking
Yui for Nana's sister?
Yui's the one I love now.
But is that because she
reminds me of Nana?
Don't worry about it too much.
The year ended with no change,
and we ended up spending New Year's Eve
and New Year's Day together.
And now we're together on the
second day of the new year too...
Two people today?
No!
What's wrong, Yui?!
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Yui?
Are you okay?
A-A man tried to...
Tried to...
Okay, I understand.
It's okay.
Calm down and take deep breaths.
So her time was reversed to the
moment right after she was assaulted.
It looks pretty bad.
I'm guessing she didn't
go to school for a while?
I need to get some fresh air.
Stop cowering like a wimp.
Huh?
You're distracting me.
Sorry.
Find something to do.
You're wasting time just sitting there.
Then I guess I'll read that book.
Wow, Inaban was cold not so long ago.
She's not a bad person,
but she can be pretty hostile.
But that doesn't change your
opinion of Inaban, does it?
No way.
Good.
Has your mom said anything
about you going out every day?
Huh?
No, not yet.
That's right.
Oh, I had my time reversed today?
How old was I?
Fourteen.
Kiriyama was also fourteen.
Yui!
Are you okay, Yui?
I remember now.
I remember everything.
I was...
Yui, it's okay. Everything's okay now.
Are you sure you can make
it home by yourself?
Uh-huh, I'm okay now.
Sorry about making such a fuss.
Mihashi-san...
Kiriyama, can you explain?
I feel uncomfortable not
knowing what happened.
But it's none of your business.
Why are you saying that?
I just want to...
Shut up!
I quit karate and that's that.
But you promised...
Stop talking about promises!
I don't want to think about the past!
Uh...
I don't know what happened before,
but Yui, you should talk
things out with Mihashi-san.
What?
I don't need you telling me what to do.
But you should hear her out.
I don't need an irresponsible
jerk ordering me around!
Irresponsible jerk?
You're nothing more than
an irresponsible jerk
who likes me because
I remind you of your ex!
Get your act together!
There's nothing wrong with me!
You're the one who
needs to get it together!
What's that mean?
You refuse to face your problems.
And that hasn't changed!
That's because I...
You're the one who makes
excuses and gives up!
I guess you're stuck with me again.
I remembered.
Huh?
My promise.
Mihashi-san and I talked
at a tournament before she moved away.
We agreed to fight each other
at the national tournament.
But I forgot all about it.
I gave up everything
meaningful in my life.
I'm like a background character now.
A background character?
Say, Taichi.
I love you, Taichi.
Huh?
Wait! Hold on a moment!
This will create lots
and lots of trouble!
Let's pretend that someone
confessed to you like that.
If you never give them an answer,
will their feelings change?
I dunno. I don't have
much experience.
Have you ever not given an answer
to someone who told you
that they love you?
If the person who confessed
their feelings first
stops expressing their love,
what is the other person
supposed to do?
That depends on what
that person wants to do.
You're right.
I used to be strong.
Not just at karate.
I was strong enough to walk on my own.
But now
I rely on everyone else to help me.
And I can't do anything in return.
I gave up my dreams and
abandoned everything
to become an empty shell.
I'm completely worthless now.
But that can't be helped,
since I was never all that
special to begin with.
Sorry you guys had to
do this for my sake.
Was this your idea, Nagase?
Uh-huh, I thought it was necessary.
I think it's better that Yui
headed home though.
You don't like Yui anymore, Aoki?
That's not it.
But my memory is a jumble
and I feel like I've forgotten
something important.
Something important?
Yeah, I'm on the verge of
remembering what that is.
I decided that I would never interfere
in someone else's relationship
since I already screwed up once.
So I won't be much help,
but I'd say that you're
thinking too much.
Thinking too much?
Thinking too much!
After all the times you hid behind your
logic and called Aoki an idiot,
that's all you have to say?!
I've changed
since I know the power of love now.
I-It's not fair to slip
stuff in like that!
You wanna talk fair?
You always act like you understand
him better than everyone else!
When did I ever do that?!
How am I supposed to react to this?
I remember.
I...
...forgot to live carefree.
Huh?
That's right.
That was the decision
I made back then.
Back then?
I'm going to go see Nana.
If something happens,
you'll have to handle it
since for some reason,
you're the only one who's
immune to time reversal.
Yeah, I got it.
Aoki, why are you going
to see Nishino-san?
To confirm my love.
What?!
Did someone cast a spell to make Aoki
look cool for a second there?!
If this means I leave StuCS,
I'll be living true to myself.
That's the path I've chosen.
When I was in middle school...
Hmm?
A girl in my class died in a car accident.
I was pretty close to her,
so it was a shock.
It made me realize that
humans can die at any time.
She attended cram school
and worked really hard.
But none of that mattered
once she was dead.
I'm not trying to say that
her effort was for nothing.
But that's why I decided to
always have as much fun as I can.
That way, I'll be happy with my
life no matter when I die.
So that's the path you've chosen?
Yeah, I don't know if
it's right or wrong.
But I'm living life to the fullest.
Whoa, it's cold!
Let's hurry.
Do you know her address?
Yeah, I brought a New
Year's card along.
Is this the right street?
Yeah, it should be around here.
Yoshifumi?
Nana...
Yoshifumi, why are you...
Sorry, I wanted to see you.
Huh?
Nana...
Y-Yes?
I really loved you.
But there's someone I love more now.
I see.
Sorry about springing this on you.
It's okay. Thanks for
coming to see me.
Who is he?
Wait, is the person you love...
Hell no!
O-Oh, that's a relief.
What are you going to do now?
Want to stop by my house?
No, I'll have to pass.
We have to catch the night bus home.
Huh?
Oh, I guess you're in a rush.
Actually...
I cut my hair towards
the end of last year.
I see.
Okay, we need to get going then.
Let's go, Taichi.
Huh? Already?
Bye.
Goodbye.
H-Hey, Aoki!
Why are you in such a hurry?!
There's still plenty
of time before noon!
I have something I need to
say as soon as possible!
Taichi! Any souvenirs?
No...
Wh-What's that?! No souvenirs?!
I told you to send a
request via e-mail.
Yui...
I believe in following whatever
I feel at the moment.
That's why I usually don't
think things through.
So when my past emotions resurfaced,
I got confused.
I wanted to confirm how I
felt, so I went to see her.
And I learned what I wanted to know.
I truly loved Nana.
I can't deny the feelings I once had,
because I was living life to the fullest.
I see...
But I'm trying even harder to do that now.
So I can't deny the feelings
I have now, either.
I once loved Nishino Nana.
And now, I love Kiriyama Yui.
Is that so wrong?
But that's because I
look like Nishino-san.
That doesn't matter.
Nana is Nana. You're you.
It wasn't your appearance.
I fell in love with you as a person...
that's the only way I can put it.
Am I worthy of someone's love?
Sure.
You're the worthiest person out there
as far as I'm concerned.
I love you, Yui,
and I wanted to remind you of that.
Pathetic! Pathetic! Pathetic!
I'm pathetic!
I always knew deep down...
I knew the truth,
but everyone was too nice,
so I didn't have to face it.
Y-Yui...
I could have explained that I was scared
of men, and worked something out!
But I didn't want to remember.
Or I thought it would
be stupid to even try.
I don't know.
But I was making excuses and giving up!
I was the one who refused
to take the last step!
I used to hate losing,
but at some point, I stopped caring.
I'm only worthless if I let myself be.
If I don't want to be a
background character,
I have to step up on stage.
Thanks to you, I'm inspired
to become strong again.
I appreciate it.
Yui, you shouldn't push yourself.
Don't stop her, Iori.
I won.
I did it.
I just had to try.
A-Are you okay?
I will never
lose again.
What is this feeling?
I haven't felt like this in forever.
The phrase "I am my own Lord throughout
heaven and earth" is perfect for me.
It even has the character
for my name in it.
Yui, if you were thinking
that phrase means that you're the best,
you're wrong.
A-Anyway, I'm...
Yoshifumi-kun, how old are you?
I'm ten.
I see...
Well, it might be hard now,
but I promise that one day
you'll know that I'm Kiriyama Yui.
I'll make sure that you
won't ever mistake me for anyone else.
Huh? Aren't you Kiriyama-san?
You look a little like Nana though.
Come with me. I'll get
you a change of clothes.
Okay.
How come he recognizes her?
Because he's sorted out his memories?
Does it matter since
everything worked out?
The rest is up to them.
Still, how long is this
phenomenon going to continue?
If it doesn't end before
school starts...
Don't worry. It shouldn't
last that long.
How can you be so sure?
Huh?
Taichi, you're hiding
something from us.
Uh, er, well...
Wh-What's wrong, Inaban?
I thought it was odd
that you were the only one
immune to time reversal.
What do you know?
What are you hiding?
That's absurd!
Mom!
Open up! It's Iori!
It was a mistake to choose you.
Wait up, idiot!
Do you want another chance?
That's impossible...
I'm...